Goddard Talk UP252
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Goddard Talk
2003 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Chaplain
UP252
0.25 Linear Feet
14 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Goddard Chapel newsletter. It is produced by the Tufts University Chaplaincy. This collection consists primarily of pdf issues of the Goddard Talk publication. In limited cases, physical copies are available also.
Biographical / Historical
Edwin Courtlandt Bolles was made the first chaplain of the university in 1905. Today, the Tufts Chaplaincy is committed to modeling interreligious harmony and well-being at Tufts. Each chaplain serves those who are in his or her tradition through regular worship and other programs. Valuing pluralism and multiculturalism, it educate tomorrows leaders for global citizenship by actively encouraging dialogue and cooperation among the wide variety of religious traditions on the campuses.
- Goddard Talk, 2003 -- 2009; UP252.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 14 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of Goddard Talk, the Goddard Chapel newsletter produced by the Tufts University Chaplaincy.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Goddard Talk, 2003; UP252.001.001.00001; Office of the University Chaplain
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Goddard Talk, 2003; UP252.001.001.00002; Office of the University Chaplain
    1, 2
  - Goddard Talk, 2004; UP252.001.001.00003; Office of the University Chaplain
    2, 1
  - Goddard Talk, 2004; UP252.001.001.00004; Office of the University Chaplain
    2, 2
  - Goddard Talk, 2005; UP252.001.001.00005; Office of the University Chaplain
    3, 1
  - Goddard Talk, Fall, 2005; UP252.001.001.00006; Office of the University Chaplain
    3, 2
  - Goddard Talk, Spring, 2006; UP252.001.001.00007; Office of the University Chaplain
    4, 1
  - Goddard Talk, Fall, 2006; UP252.001.001.00008; Office of the University Chaplain
    4, 2
  - Goddard Talk, Spring, 2007; UP252.001.001.00009; Office of the University Chaplain
    5, 1
  - Goddard Talk, Fall, 2007; UP252.001.001.00010; Office of the University Chaplain (Box 1)
    5, 2
  - Goddard Talk, Spring, 2008; UP252.001.001.00011; Office of the University Chaplain
    6, 1
  - Goddard Talk, Fall, 2008; UP252.001.001.00012; Office of the University Chaplain
    6, 2
  - Goddard Talk, 2009-01; UP252.001.001.00013; Office of the University Chaplain
    7, 1
  - Goddard Talk, 2009-09; UP252.001.001.00014; Office of the University Chaplain
    7, 2